 {

      "category":
            "Politics",
      "questions":
          [
            {
               "answer": "Fidel Castro",
               "question": "Who is the dictator of Cuba?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Saddam Hussain",
               "question": "Who was the dictator of Iraq?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Texas",
               "question": "In which state was George W Bush governor before becoming President of the United States?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Arkansas",
               "question": "In which state was Bill Clinton governor before becoming President of the United States?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "In the year 1990",
               "question": "In what year became John Major the leader of the Conservative Party?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "In the year 1961",
               "question": "In what year was the Berlin wall built?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Tito",
               "question": "Jozip Broz was formerly a Yugoslav marshal and statesman. He became prime minister in 1945 and president in 1953. Give a more familiar name."
             },
            {
               "answer": "Sufragettes",
               "question": "How were called the British women who fought for women s suffrage?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Salazar",
               "question": "Who was the Portuguese dictator at the time of Franco?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Agent Orange",
               "question": "What is the defoliant called that was used in Vietnam?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Dutch language",
               "question": "What is the most spoken language in Belgium?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Four heads",
               "question": "How many heads of presidents are carved into Mount Rushmore?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Seven years",
               "question": "For how many years is a French president elected?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Spencer Percival",
               "question": "Who is the only British Prime Minister to be murdered?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Ukraine",
               "question": "In which country happened the Orange Revolution between 2004-2005?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Poland",
               "question": "Which country had a Prime Minister and President who were twin brothers?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "George Washington",
               "question": "Which American president appears on a one dollar bill?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "California",
               "question": "For which state did Arnold Schwarzenegger become governor in November 2003?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Walker",
               "question": "What does the \"W\" in the name George W Bush stand for?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "The White House",
               "question": "In which house does the American president live?"
             }
          ]
    }